Still
The space and the time
Dancing the floor like
Shadows entwined
Forget about us
Lone on the mountain
Lost to the sound
I can't feel enough
To bear the weight of us
To keep this wasted love
I can't feel enough
This love ain't mine
Calm
A rippling lake
The faces that taunt me
Keep guiding my way
What happened to us?
Torn from the moment
All written in dust
I can't feel enough
To bear the weight of us
To keep this wasted love
I can't feel enough
To bear the weight of us
To keep this wasted love
I can't feel enough
It's all one
You know now (I can't feel enough)
It's not over
Just gone now (I can't feel enough)
What goes round
Comes back around
This love ain't mine